Hello.
In this next lecture, I'm going to go over how to fix the problems that I mentioned in the previous
lecture.
So the first problem was the apple and the enemy projector.
It just overlaps with our level.
In order to fix this, let's first select our level and under search workflow attack and then go create
new tag and cool this level.
We're going to make it so that if our project are something with the level tag, it will become destroyed.
Let's first start off with our apple.
If we open up the Apple product, our blueprint, we made it so that if anything with the tag enemy
overlaps, if we apply damage to it and then destroy the actor.
We're going to add some nodes to this blueprint.
So if we just drag off the actor, look for actor as tag.
And if an actor has a tag, which is level.
Or enemy, then we're going to apply diamonds to it and then destroy our own actor.
So if we look for all bullion and just connect this into hair and that's into hair, then we can go
compile.
Next if we find our mushroom projectile.
We made it.
So if the motion projector overlaps our player character.
We do do once.
Then we apply damage to our player character and then make the mushroom to its mushroom, destroy the
animation.
Then we destroy it.
So if they overlap something which is not equal to our black actor, we want to drag off other actor
and check to see if it overlaps our level.
So look for actor as tag.
For the attack.
We have to type in level and then we want to drag off here and look for Branch.
Just connect folks into here and then true into the set flip book, because we don't want to damage
our player character.
If this fear overlaps the level, we can go compile and just test that.
This all works.
So if I go play.
And I threw my apple up the world.
It gets destroyed when the enemy projectile hits the world, it becomes destroyed.
And with this, we have fixed the first issue.
The second issue is that my player character is no longer getting a screen check effect when they get
damaged.
To fix this, if we go back to our player blueprint.
Whenever I play a character that becomes damaged, we play this world camera shake and we made the outer
radius of this 1100.
But because I increased the spring arm of my camera, I made the camera much further away.
So we need to increase the outer radius so it can still reach our camera.
Let's type in 1500, then go to play.
And now I've become damaged.
Okay, so I don't think that I was far enough.
So if I increase this to something like 1900.
I could play.
When I become damaged, we can see we have the screen camera effect.
So depending on your distance from the camera, you may need to play around with this value again.
But then finally, when our tone died, it could still attack me.
So we open up a skeleton blueprint and I'm just going to decrease its health because I gave mine a lot
of health.
Some of it get poor.
Then we go over to the custom event scanner to attack.
If our scanner is dead.
So I'll look for that.
Is that viable?
Then we're not going to allow our skeleton to attack.
So I drag up it and look for Branch.
And if this is true, then we'll do nothing.
However, if this is false, then we'll allow our scantling to attack so I can go compile play.
And now if I attack my skeleton.
They should not be able to attack me when it dies.
Okay, nice with this.
We have fixed all the issues that I wanted to fix.